<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Ali Pirani</title>
    <link>https://alipirani88.github.io/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Ali Pirani</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://alipirani88.github.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Test New Content</title>
      <link>https://alipirani88.github.io/post/2020-03-11-test-new-page/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alipirani88.github.io/post/2020-03-11-test-new-page/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reproducible Research Tools 2</title>
      <link>https://alipirani88.github.io/2019/09/24/conda-containers-cwl/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alipirani88.github.io/2019/09/24/conda-containers-cwl/</guid>
      <description>This post is about the presentation where I talked about Reproducible Research tools that researchers in the field of Bioinformatics/Sceince are currently using to improve reproducibility, reusability and transparency in their research. Many of our data analysis process contain a mixture of systems, commands and libraries which demands a workflow system to log or manage our daily activities. Just like a wet lab personnel who maintains a lab notebook to jot down the methods/steps that they used to generate the results, it is necessary for a dry lab personnel to log each and every step, commands and system that they used that helped them generate the final results.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to Ali&#39;s Blog</title>
      <link>https://alipirani88.github.io/2019/09/15/hello-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alipirani88.github.io/2019/09/15/hello-world/</guid>
      <description>  “Yeah It&amp;rsquo;s on. ”
 Hello World! </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Clean White Theme for Hugo</title>
      <link>https://alipirani88.github.io/post/readme/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alipirani88.github.io/post/readme/</guid>
      <description>Clean White Theme for Hugo CleanWhite is a clean, elegant, but fully functional blog theme for Hugo. Here is a live demo site using this theme.
It is based on huxblog Jekyll Theme and Clean Blog Jekyll Theme.
These two upstream projects have done awesome jobs to create a blog theme, what I&amp;rsquo;m doing here is porting it to Hugo, of which I like the simplicity and the much faster compiling speed.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>